

# Nijat Hamid Frontend - React Developer

#### How to reach me:

#### Phone:

(+994) 55-637-51-69

#### Email:

nicatorium@gmail.com

#### Github:

https://github.com/Nijat-Hamid

#### Linkedin:

@nijat-hamid

#### Facebook:

@nicatorium

# Language

- Azerbaijani (Native)
- Turkish (Professional working proficiency)
- English (B1-Intermediate)

# **Education History**

#### **Master Degree:**

Azerbaijan State Oil and Industry University

- Electronics Engineering
- Attended since Sept. 2019 to May 2021
- Taking up electives in engineering

# **Bachelor Degree:**

National Aviation Academy

- Telecommunacation,
   Electronics Engineering
- Attended from Sept. 2015 to May 2019
- In-depth study of electronics and telecommunications networks.

#### **Personal Profile**

Hello. I'm Nijat Hamid. I work as a Frontend React developer. After working in the field of Digital Marketing for a long time, I chose to continue my career as a Frontend Developer.

The Javascript programming language is now a big part of my life. I aim to be one of the most distinguished experts in this field. Let's talk then:)

### **Professional Skills**

## Major Tech Stack:

HTML5, CSS3, SASS/SCSS Bootstrap, Jquery, Javascript, React, React Hooks, Redux Toolkit Reactbootstrap, MUI, Figma, Git/Github

### **Minor Tech Stack:**

Tailwind, ViteJS, Gulp, Material Design Lite, Ajax, Headless UI, Zeplin, Sketch, Module CSS, Styled Components, WoW / AoS / Gsap Animations, Trello/Notion/Slack

#### **Other Skills Stacks:**

SEO Optimization
Wordpress Development
Content Manager
Google Analytics & Search
Console
Premier Pro, Photoshop, After
Effects
Office Suite
Social Media Marketing
IT Help Desk

## **Soft Skills**

- Problem-Solving / Critical Thinking
- · Researcher soul
- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Openness to criticism
- Communication
- Open-Mindedness
- Time Management
- Adaptability

#### **Career Summary**

### **Tedroid - Tech Media Platform**

- Co-Founder (Apr 2022-Present)
- Wordpress Developer
- SEO Specialist
- · Content Manager

https://www.tedroid.com

# TelSat MMC (EraSoft MMC)

- Content Manager (Jan 2022-June 2022)
- Bug Tester
- · SEO Specialist

My Content Portfolio: https://telsat.az/az/xeberler/

#### **Technote MMC**

- SEO Specialist (2021)
- Video Editor (2020- 2021)
- Content Manager & SMM ( 2019-2021)

My Content Portfolio: <a href="https://technote.az/editor/nijat-hamid">https://technote.az/editor/nijat-hamid</a>

# **Freelance Works**

- Azercell
  - o Press Release & Content Creator
- Huawei
  - o Content & Concept Creator
- HyperX
  - Content Creator
- Huawei
  - o Content Creator
- Intel
  - Review & Content Creator
- Kontakt Home
  - Project Based
- AzBadam MMC
  - Content Creator
- Technote MMC
  - Project based
- EraSoft MMC
  - Project Based
- VipEx Kargo
- SEO & Content